+88 01727244864

joyonto.karmakar.cse@gmail.com

github.com/Joyontokarmakar

() joyontokarmakar.netlify.app 0

linkedin.com/in/joyontokarmakar

## in

# Front end Web Developer

Joyonto Karmakar

### PROFILE

I am a Front-end Developer and I love to do coding also I counted myself as a dedicated and hardworking person, I created lots of successful websites that are fast, easy to use, and built with my best try. I used HTML, CSS, CSS Framework and Library, JavaScript and JavaScript Framework also library and JavaScript wrapper and also to produce responsive websites and web apps that provide users the best and most appropriate experience suited to their device and browser.

### EXPERIENCE

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER - (02/2021 - PRESENT)

JATRI SERVICES LIMITED - Dhaka, Bangladesh

Conceptualized digital creative campaigns and initiatives in close collaboration with Development team. Pinpointed user experience issues to device targeted suggestions for creating a cohesive user experience

**FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER (INTERN) -** (07/2020 – 01/2021)

**CODERSPY IT SOLUTION LIMITED** - Dhaka, Bangladesh

Make the frontend of website lucrative and responsive for all device and up to max 5000px screen resolution.

### **PROJECTS**

#### **ONLINE USER TICKETING WEBSITE**

% LIVE SITE LINK: brothersnavigation.com ✓

TECHNOLOGY USE: Nuxt Js, Vue Js-2, Tailwind Css, Ssl-Commerze Payment Gateway.

🗐 DESCRIPTION: User Can Buy Their Launch Journey Ticket Through This Website. User No Need To Log In Here. User Can Pay By Ssl Commerze Payment Gateway. After Purchasing Successfully A Ticket User Can Print His/Her Ticket From The Website.

### **EDUCATION**

**BSC IN CSE** (2017-2021)

SOUTHEAST UNIVERSITY

Dhaka, Bangladesh

HIGHER SECONDERY (2013-2015)

SHAHID SYED NAZRUL ISLAM COLLEGE

Mymensingh, Bangladesh

### SKILLS

#### #Comfortable

NUXT JS, Vue JS, JavaScript, ES6, Tailwind CSS

#### #Familiar

React JS, Bootstrap5, JQuery, HTML5, CSS

#### #Others

Github, Postman, Wordpress, Shopify, SASS, C, C++

#### **CATERING SERVICE WEBSITE**

**%** LIVE SITE LINK: mama-s-catering.web.app ✓

**○ Code:** </> Client side </> Server side

TECHNOLOGY USE: React JS, Node JS, React Bootstrap, Express JS, Mongo DB, Firebase.

**DESCRIPTION:** Admin can upload service and can make new admin and can update the ordered product status. User can choose and buy product from the product list. Amin and User both will be authenticate in this website by login systemSuccessfully A Ticket User Can Print His/Her Ticket From The Website.

#### **ONLINE VEGETABLE SHOP**

% LIVE SITE LINK: veg-green.web.app ✓

Code: </> Client side </> Server side

**TECHNOLOGY USE:** React JS, Node JS, React Bootstrap, Mongo DB, Firebase...

DESCRIPTION: A User can choose his/her preferable product from the list. Then if he/she theis logged in already they will be permitted to enter the checkout page otherwise he/she needs to log in. Then they will redirect to the order page and now they can order the product. Admin can Add, Delete, and Edit the product.

### CERTIFICATIONS & AWARDS

**COMPLETE WEB DEVELOPMENT -** (12/2020 – 03/2021)

PROGRAMMING HERO COMMUNITY

**RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN - (09/2018 – 12/2018)** 

CODERS TRUST BANGLADESH

**TOP CONTRIBUTOR - (08/2018)** 

**GOOGLE CROWDSOURCE** 

INTRA UNIVERSITY MATH OLYMPIAD (RANK-4TH)- (09/ 2017)

SOUTHEAST UNIVERSITY